This is the Emerald Editing Team.
Also known as "The Maiden Club."
Apparently, they're also called "The Hot Guy Collection..."
Excuse me.
I believe I told you all that today is the deadline for the manuscript...
So why isn't anyone finished?!
Huh?
The deadline's today?
How many times have I told you?!
Just yesterday, I reminded you all repeatedly!
I don't remember that.
Me neither.
They're not taking me seriously...
tatoe moshi kimi ga sekai no hate ni itemo
Even if you go to the ends of the earth
ima sugu ni mitsukeru yo
I would find you right away
osaekirenai kodou
I can't control my emotions
doko ni itatte wakatte shimau
No matter where you go, I always know where you are
afuredashita shousoukan
Uneasiness fills me
itsu kara koi tte kizuiteta
When did I realize it was love?
yarinaoshitai
I want to redo it
kinou ga furagu da tte iu nara
If you tell me yesterday was the flag
mainichi nando demo kasanetai yo
I want to repeat that day over and over
tatoe moshi kimi ga sekai no hate ni itemo
Even if you go to the ends of the earth
ima sugu ni mitsukeru kara
I would find you right away
koi wa mujun darake sae
Even if love is full of contradictions,
kimi no kimochi wo kikaseteyo
I want you to tell me your feelings
kitto futari yatto soko kara hajimaru ne
Surely that's what will bring us together
kitsuzen ni te wo nobasun da
I'll work up the courage and reach out to you
Even though I'm new to manga editing,
I was recently promoted to program director for the magazine.
It's the program director's job
to regulate the production schedule up until the magazine's release date.
Printer
He consults with the printer to set the
schedule up to the point of proofreading,
Printer
Editors
and the editors gather the manga artists' manuscripts accordingly.
Editorss
Editors
Printer
Afterward, he submits the materials to the printer.
I guess Takano gave me this position because
he wanted me to learn the flow of magazine publishing. Still...
What am I supposed to do without my manuscripts?!
I'll go make ya a copy.
'Kay.
You guys need to get your act together.
Don't give Onodera too much trouble.
Hatori!
You're one to talk.
When it comes to breaking deadlines, your artist is a serial offender.
Not this time.
I made sure there was plenty of extra time.
Really?
That's great news!
What time do you think you can get the manuscript to me?
Hatori.
You received a fax.
Thank you.
Mr. Hatori,
I was struck by a sudden fever and cold symptoms this morning,
so I don't think the manuscript will be done in time.
Due to this, please don't come near my apartment for a while.
Don't send me emails or call me either.
Thank you!
Chiaki Yoshino
I'm terribly sorry.
Chiharu Yoshikawa just asked me to come over this very moment.
I'm leaving now.
Bye, then.
What about the manuscript?
Sorry.
It probably won't get done for a while.
What?
What's this?
I told everyone that we had to meet this deadline!
Am I being bullied?
Are they bullying me?!
What am I going to do?
I already promised it to the printer.
This is...
You know...
It's good that you're enthusiastic,
but when will you finally realize that it's weird for the printer to set the deadline for today?
Huh?
Go back to our past releases to get an idea of the schedule.
How many days does it take to collect the stuff, print, and deliver it?
What?
Look, it's set early.
I bet you just agreed to the printer's conditions without another word.
My point is that the printer isn't taking you seriously.
Yay! Rittie got fooled.
B-But...
Excuse me for saying this,
but what's wrong with getting it done earlier?
Then everybody will be happy and—
Are you an idiot?
94% of an editor's job is to
take the manuscript from the reluctant author, by any means necessary!
You should also make the printer wait until the very last minute and force the manuscript into the production!
Is that really what an editor's job is?
I'll have to call the printer by tomorrow
and negotiate an extension.
Ugh, I feel so tired.
I guess they were screwing with me.
Onodera.
Yes?
Samples of Mutou's newest book just arrived.
I'll leave them here.
Right, thank you!
Love Star
Yukina Mutou's
____long-awaited new work!!
Wow!
These are the first volumes I ever edited!
They should be in stores in about a week or so.
Uh oh, I'm so happy about this that I might go check out the first day sales.
It's like my bad mood just melted away.
Well, I don't have anything else to do today,
so I'm going to leave work on a high note.
Uh... Takano?
The samples of Mutou's latest book are here.
I left them on your desk.
Are you going home?
Yeah.
I'm going now.
Hey.
What are you...
Fuzz.
This was in your hair all day!
That's what you get for sleeping on the floor.
Excuse me, but I happen to sleep in a bed.
Liar.
I'm not lying!
Goodbye.
If you slept at my place, I'd wake you up whenever you wanted.
What the hell is he thinking, saying stuff like that?
What if somebody heard him?
I don't want people touching me.
I've been trying my hardest to forget how close we became the other night...
But I still remember how it felt when he touched me.
How it felt when he kissed me,
put his arms around me...
And then...
Hey, hey, hey!
I've got to pull myself together!
He was basically forcing himself on me!
It's not that I like him or anything!
One Week Later
How Much Would
It Cost To Actually
Keep A Pet Panda?
How Much Would
It Cost To Actually
Keep A Pet Panda?
I ended up coming to the store the day they released it.
How Much Would
It Cost To Actually
Keep A Pet Panda?
How Much Would
It Cost To Actually
Keep A Pet Panda?
How Much Would
It Cost To Actually
Keep A Pet Panda?
How Much Would
It Cost To Actually
Keep A Pet Panda?
How Much Would
It Cost To Actually
Keep A Pet Panda?
How Much Would
It Cost To Actually
Keep A Pet Panda?
I guess I'm curious to see how well it sells.
How Much Would
It Cost To Actually
Keep A Pet Panda?
How Much Would
It Cost To Actually
Keep A Pet Panda?
How Much Would
It Cost To Actually
Keep A Pet Panda?
How Much Would
It Cost To Actually
Keep A Pet Panda?
Did you buy this month's Emerald?
Yeah! Wasn't it cute?
They're here!
Yeah!
I could really use one of those.
Me, too!
Oh, Love Star is out!
All right!
Wish
Please buy it!
It's really good!
Wish
Buy it! Buy it!
Hey!
Wish
What are you doing here?
Well, what are you doing here?
Work reasons.
You should stop playing hooky.
I'm not!
I just came to see how Mutou's newest book was doing.
How it's doing?
Yes, you know.
Like seeing how many copies have sold.
What the hell?
Are you a rookie?
Hey!
This store sells a lot of our works, so I thought I should
come and introduce my—
Now, look here.
That's sales' job.
You're an editor. Stay the hell out of it.
It's annoying.
Mr. Yokozawa!
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
It's not a problem at all.
Oh, yes. Why don't I introduce you two?
This is Onodera, the editor of Love Star,
the book that was released today.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Onodera.
Nice to meet you, too.
Mutou's last work did quite well, which is why I ordered a lot of copies this time.
I'm really sorry.
I feel like I caused you extra work.
Seriously.
I'll just tell you one more thing.
Leave that residence.
What?
Your presence messes with him.
I'm sorry, but I don't quite understand what you're trying to say.
Shut up.
I'm telling you to move out.
Excuse me, but your attitude is really starting to annoy me!
I keep telling you over and over.
There is nothing going on between me and Takano!
It's really weird of you to tell me to move out!
If anyone is getting annoyed, it's me.
I don't understand why you insist on treating me like your enemy.
Could it be that the two of you were going out?
Is that why you're so persistent?
And what if we were?
What... did he just say?
Hello?
Oh, yes.
Tonight?
And what if we were?
I understand. That's fine. I'll go.
What?
So those two were...
Be on time. You're always late,
Masamune.
That was Takano, right?
It's none of your business.
If what he said before was true,
it was because of me that Takano went off the edge,
and it was Yokozawa who saved him.
Are they together now?
No, Takano's not the kind of guy
who would say he loved me if they were.
Then again, the Takano I knew was the one back in high school.
I don't know anything about him now.
It's not like I give a damn anyway!
So...
why does my heart feel all funny?
Will you guys please get your act together?!
Just when do you plan on having your manuscripts ready for me?!
How should I know?
What about you, Hatori?
What's going on with Yoshikawa's manuscript?
He pissed me off, so I haven't contacted him in a while.
Well, contact him now!
Yes?
Yes, it's me!
Thank you for all your help!
Shit, it's the printer!
Yes, I'm so sorry.
Actually, we don't have it yet.
Yes, yes. Yes, I'm terribly sorry.
Ah, well of course—
Yes.
Are you still going to the gym?
Oh I see, you're thinner now!
That's great!
My stomach hurts.
I never thought being the program director would be this stressful.
Everybody's treating me like a total rookie and giving me the run around.
I guess it's my fault for not being able to do the job right...
And then on the way home, I went to that bar,
and Mr. Yokozawa and Mr. Takano were there!
Really? No way!
You should've called me!
So they did meet up last night.
The two of them.
What's the big idea?!
What is this?
It's a manual on how to deal with the printer.
I wrote it step by step, so just follow those instructions.
Huh?
You're just way too straightforward.
At this rate, you're going to be at the mercy of the printer forever.
Just watching you irritates me.
Hey!
That's mine!
And there was a call about Mutou's latest book.
They said they might have to do another run.
Really?
That's great!
Want to go get dinner?
Huh?
To celebrate the release of your first work and the additional run.
Well, I guess it'll just be drinks with our team.
Uh... well, um... That's...
Thank you very much, but that's not necessary.
Okay, then.
Make sure you're ready to leave by nine.
I'll tell the others as well.
Wait! Takano!
He really is unbelievable.
And here I am on the last train.
Everyone was all, "Yay, let's celebrate the additional run!"
I'd prefer if they would get their manuscripts together first!
I did everything Takano's note told me to,
and the negotiations went fine.
I'm glad it worked out. It's just that...
I guess it's also somewhat frustrating
that I couldn't resolve the problem myself.
Yes?
It's me.
Takano!
Where are you?
Wh-Why do you ask?
I told you we would celebrate this.
Everything's closed, so I'm getting stuff from the convenience store.
I'm at the convenience store in front of the station.
Oh, I'm very sorry!
I actually just left the office,
which means that—
Potato Chips
First love's...
Kumazu
Convenience
Congratulations on the release of your first work,
and on getting the additional run.
Thank you very much.
See, I knew it!
The two of us have absolutely nothing interesting to talk about!
That reminds me.
You went to the store the day of the release, didn't you?
H-How do you know that?
Yokozawa told me.
I don't care one way or the other.
I'm sure you know, but that's sales' territory, so tread lightly.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
I can feel myself getting irritated.
You don't have to apologize.
We have a ton of unpleasant things that we could talk about,
but it's not like I can ask him about those things,
so I get more and more irritated.
In the end, I don't know Takano at all,
and all of this meaningless stuff is just flying around in my head.
I bet people don't like drinking with you.
Whaaddaa you saaay?!
Obnoxious and whiny. You're the worst drunk ever.
Shudaaaaap!
So youda chief editor! Think I givva damn?!
You're cut off.
Hey, give baack...
I said you're done.
Lemme drink!
Hey! Onodera, stop!
Wadda waste...
Could ya... not... do that?
I mean, you're already going out with Yokozawa.
I'm amazed you can do this.
If you're already with someone, you should stop going after me.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Yokozawa told me the whole thing!
And then the girl from general affairs saw you two at the bar.
It makes sense.
Whenever he's around,
you always look like you're having so much fun,
but I guess it's fun to be with the person you love.
You're drunk.
I'm not drunk!
I'm going home.
Man.
What am I going to do with you?
Here's a towel.
Dry off.
Don't touch me!
Maybe it doesn't mean anything to you, but I'm not like that.
Hey.
I just want this to be about work.
Onodera.
I'm just a joke to you.
At work, too. You're always yanking my chain.
Onodera!
I can't take it anymore!
Every time the smallest thing happens, I can't stop agonizing over it.
How do you think I feel?
Why...
Why do I have to get irritated over something like this?
I'm going home.
Hey, Onodera.
Wait!
Let me go.
Now just a—
You think having you around doesn't affect me at all?
But...
I'm not jerking you around.
If the person you love is in front of you, at work or wherever,
you can't keep it contained at all times.
So don't provoke me.
Because I won't be able to stop myself.
Stop! Stop it!
Why are you doing this?!
You're in love with Yokozawa!
Hey.
I don't know what you've heard,
but stop jumping to conclusions.
I'm saying that you're the one I love.
And if you can say all that, why not just admit it?
You love me, don't you?
I keep telling you that I love you. What else do you want?
If you're saying it's still not enough,
then how much do I have to love you in order for you to let me in?
Onodera.
Remember this. I don't care if you have a fiancée or not, I...
Saga...
Ritsu.
I love you.
Um, this situation...
I do remember that I toasted with Takano, at his place, to celebrate.
And?
I don't recall a thing that happened after that!
You're finally up.
Uh, good morning.
I'm sorry.
I have this habit of taking off my clothes when I'm drunk.
You don't remember?
Remember what?
You seriously don't remember?
I'm sorry, did I do something?
You really are horrible.
What?
Anyway, I'm going home.
It looks like I stayed too long anyway. I'm sorr—
Ache
My hips...
Wait, I don't think so, but did Takano and I...?
No. No way!
That's totally impossible!
Anyway, what did you and Yokozawa talk about?
Huh? Wh-What are you talking about?
You want to ask me about something, right?
What? No, nothing.
I think you're misunderstanding something.
Excuse me.
I'll tell you just one thing then.
You seem to like me more than you think.
What? What gave you that idea?!
If you want to know more, just remember last night.
Yeah, right!
Please keep your fantasies in check!
Maybe you had a weird dream.
If you have time to come up with stuff like that,
how about getting your manuscript already?
Your manuscript is the last one missing!
Excuse me!
He pisses me off.
What am I going to do?
I really can't remember a thing.
I really don't think so, but what if...?
What if I...?
No, no, no! Never!
There's no way that could have happened!
It was a dream!
Everything up until now was a dream!
I will force myself to believe that!
zutto tsutaetai no wa todoketai no wa
What I always want to tell you, what I want you to understand
tada hitotsu no I love you
are just the words "I love you"
okuru no wa zutto kimi dake ni
You're always the only one I want to understand
J
doushou mo nai tomerarenai
I can't help it, I can't stop it
J
kono kanjou no namae nante wakaranai
I don't even know what this feeling is called
J
ochitsukanai nemurenai
I can't calm down, I can't sleep
J
mou nanimo atama ni hairanai
I can't cram anything else into my head
J
te wo gutto nobaseba furesou na yubi de
When I reach out with trembling fingers
J
tada soko mitsumeteru kokoro ga sawaideru
you're just there, looking at me, and my heart leaps
zutto tsutaetai no wa todoketai no wa
What I always want to tell you, what I want you to understand
tada hitotsu no I love you
are just the words "I love you"
ima nanji
"What time is it?"
choushi dou dai
"How are you doing?"
sonna n ja nakute sa
That's not what I wanted to say!
itsumo mune no naka de sakende n da yo
Inside my heart I'm constantly yelling
akireru hodo I love you
the words "I love you" so loud it shocks me
okuru no wa zutto kimi dake ni
You're always the only one I want to understand.
Next Time Preview
Marukawa Publishing Glossary #12
Today's word is "Marukawa Publishing."
Marukawa is a publishing house that releases manga and novels.
The genres covered are literature, shojo manga, shounen manga,
seinen manga,and even boys' love and much more.
It's the first publisher for the author Akihiko Usami,
and the super popul—